<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Gray Analytics</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Gray Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Synthesis Part 1</title>
      <link>/2018/02/25/data-synthesis-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/25/data-synthesis-part-1/</guid>
      <description>This post is less of a how to and more of an algorithm idea.
Inspired by random walk and monte carlo, I wanted to write an algorithm that could be used to synthetically upsample data that is a mixture of factoral and numeric data, where the columns are not independent.
My original hope was to synthesize factoral combinations.
But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. Without outside knowledge of what factorial column combinations are allowed, I have to work with the combinations present in the input data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Serverless Database on a Windows Machine</title>
      <link>/2018/02/15/setting-up-a-serverless-database-on-a-windows-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/15/setting-up-a-serverless-database-on-a-windows-machine/</guid>
      <description>This is a bit of an &amp;lsquo;infrastructure&amp;rsquo; post. Helping develop a working environment for future projects.
I prefer storing data in a database vs txt files. But that&amp;rsquo;s me.
Educators My primary source for this is SQLite&amp;rsquo;s quickstart page website.
Tool I briefly considered three databases for this:
 Oracle Lite
 Looks like this requires you to setup a mini-server function on your PC. Sounds like a pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Blog</title>
      <link>/2018/02/11/how-to-make-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/11/how-to-make-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>FIRST POST!!! I made a blog, it makes sense that if I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;lsquo;Learning out Loud&amp;rsquo;, my first post should contain what I learned on &amp;lsquo;How to Make a Blog&amp;rsquo;. And based on how poorly this post looks, you know i&amp;rsquo;m not lying about the &amp;lsquo;First Post&amp;rsquo; comment.
Educators My primary source for this is Yihui Xie&amp;rsquo;s website.
Getting Started I&amp;rsquo;m using RStudio as my primary editor.
So you&amp;rsquo;ll want to install</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>